hey it's josephine from the point shop i am at dance medical in san diego and you
嘿，我是 point shop 的约瑟芬，我在圣地亚哥的舞蹈医疗中心工作，你
have been loving our instagram reels so i wanted to give you some background
一直很喜欢我们的 instagram 卷轴，所以我想给你一些
story on one of the reels that i made while i was fitting so this dancer came
关于我在试衣时制作的一个卷轴的背景故事，所以这位舞者
in with the longest most beautiful legs gorgeous gorgeous feet and she was
进来了 最长的最美丽的腿华丽的双脚，她
telling me that she was in a professional ballet company and she's
告诉我她在一家专业的芭蕾舞团工作，但
still having trouble articulating her feet and getting over her box i had her
她的脚仍然无法清晰地表达并越过她的盒子 我让她
put on her current point shoes and she clearly wasn't getting over the box
穿上她现在的尖鞋，她显然没有得到
and it was also twisting a lot she grew up in a professional ballet school which
她在专业芭蕾舞学校长大，这也
means that it's a ballet school that's connected with a professional company
意味着这是一所与专业公司有联系的芭蕾舞学校，
and a lot of these schools have certain brands that they really like so this
其中很多学校都有他们非常喜欢的某些品牌，所以这位
dancer grew up wearing just one type of brand if you're just flexible and not
舞者从小就穿着 只有一种品牌如果你只是灵活而不
strong you may not be able to get over on your point shoes if you're just
强壮，你可能无法克服你的点鞋如果你只是
strong and not flexible then you may not get on point but this girl had
强壮而不灵活，那么你可能无法获得点bu 这个女孩
everything so what is the problem here this dancer has really wide feet and a
什么都有所以这里有什么问题这个舞者的脚真的很宽而且
really high profile so there was just a lot of volume in her foot the point
非常高所以她的脚有很多体积
shoes that she was in unfortunately doesn't come in wider widths so the
不幸的是她穿的尖头鞋没有更宽的宽度所以
widest width in that particular brand just wasn't wide enough for her we tried
那个特定品牌中最宽的宽度对她来说不够宽我们尝试
a brand that was two widths wider than what she was in and she was able to get
了一个比她所在的宽度宽两个宽度的品牌她能够很好地
over beautifully she was able to balance really well and she's strong enough and
克服她能够很好地保持平衡而且她足够强壮
that's how we get her over her point shoes a lot of people come into
这就是如何 我们让她超越了她的点鞋很多人都
our point you fitting with a solution they say that i think the vamp is too
同意我们的观点，你有一个解决方案他们说我认为鞋面
short or i think the shank is too soft or the shank is too hard you have to
太短或我认为鞋面太软或鞋面太硬你必须
come in with the problem because the solution may be different for every
进来 问题是因为每个人的解决方案可能都不同，
single person you might not be getting over your box too but you may have
你可能也无法克服你的盒子，但你可能有
completely different reasons why you're not getting over a lot of people when
完全不同的原因为什么当他们看到他们没有克服你的很多人时
they see that they're not getting over your point shoes they keep giving you
你没有克服点 nt 鞋 他们一直给你
softer shoes because it's easier to bend and that's
更柔软的鞋，因为它更容易弯曲，
that works most of the time but it could also be because the vamp is too short
这在大多数情况下都有效，但也可能是因为鞋面
the crown is too low the shoe is too narrow the shoe is too tapered the shoe
太短，冠部太低，鞋太窄，鞋太锥形，鞋
is too hard the shoe is too soft i mean there's a million different reasons why
是 太硬 鞋子太软 我的意思是有一百万种不同的原因导致
you may not be getting over your box and for this particular dancer that wasn't
你无法克服你的盒子，对于这个根本不是解决方案的特定舞者来说，
the solution at all it almost didn't matter how soft or how hard the shoes
鞋子有多软或多硬几乎无关紧要
were we just had to figure out the shape of the shoe and once we're able to
我们只需要弄清楚鞋子的形状，一旦我们能够
figure out the shape then we were able to get her over on their box sometimes
弄清楚形状，我们就可以让她在他们的盒子上，有时
it's just as simple as going for a wider width if the shoe doesn't fit width-wise
如果鞋子没有，这就像选择更宽的宽度一样简单 宽度合适，
then it might pull you back and this girl is a professional dancer at a very
那么它可能会把你拉回来，这个女孩是一家非常
prestigious contemporary ballet company she had to get to this level to figure
有声望的当代芭蕾舞团的专业舞者，她必须达到这个水平才能
out that her shoes didn't fit so whenever you have a problem don't come
弄清楚她的鞋子不合脚，所以当你有问题时不要
into your fitter with the solution tell them what your problems are we'll try to
使用解决方案 tel 进入您的装配工 l他们你的问题是什么我们会尽力
figure out the best solution for you
为你找出最好的解决方案
[Music]
[音乐]